[
  {
    "question": "How many nationalities do we have?",
    "answers": ["5", "10", "15"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the person who had the idea to open the office in Spain?",
    "answers": ["Khaled", "Paula", "Mateo"],
    "correctAnswer": "Paula"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people are working from the Valencia?",
    "answers": ["20", "30", "50"],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the dish that we love to eat the most?",
    "answers": ["Paella", "Arroz al Horno", "Waffles"],
    "correctAnswer": "Paella"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many departments we have present?",
    "answers": ["4", "5", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the christmas gathering event?",
    "answers": ["Flutter Valencia", "International cusine", "JAT"],
    "correctAnswer": "JAT"
  },
  {
    "question": "What department has most members in the office?",
    "answers": ["WE", "DiE", "MX"],
    "correctAnswer": "DiE"
  },
  {
    "question": "For how long we keep the 'fallas going out' tradition?",
    "answers": ["2 years", "3 years", "5 years"],
    "correctAnswer": "3 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who loves to cook paella for us?",
    "answers": ["Samuel", "Elias", "Marta"],
    "correctAnswer": "Samuel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helps around with finance?",
    "answers": ["Yoana", "Elias", "Sonia"],
    "correctAnswer": "Sonia"
  }
]